欢迎喜欢的朋友加入familyguy百度贴吧共同讨论
或加FG粉丝交流 QQ群 165859780
It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
今晚的头条新闻 我们继续追踪报道
Our top story tonight, we continue to track
飓风Flozell的行程
the progress of Hurricane Flozell.
这场虚构的飓风在Seth的三部剧中都出现过
《American Dad》《Family Guy》《The Cleveland Show》
播出一个月前弗吉尼亚州和罗德岛州都受到了飓风"艾琳"的影响
国家气象局
The National Weather Service
发布了严重的飓风预警
has issued a Severe Hurricane Advisory,
强烈建议民众呆在室内
and is urging everyone to stay indoors
至少接下来36小时内不要出门
for at least the next 36 hours.
不…怎么回事
No...! What happened?!
一定是大风吹得卫星信号接收器松掉了
The wind must have knocked the satellite dish loose.
啊 我日 我还准备看《G.I. Jose》呢
Aw, crap. And I was going to watch G.I. Jose.
"G.I. Jose:真正的墨西哥英雄"恶搞了"G.I. Joe:真正的美国英雄"
是剧中设定的一个玩具同名真人角色 常教给小孩子们一些生活常识
G.I.Joe早年天朝引进过其部分动画 译名为特种部队
哎呀 你把额头摔破了
Oh, no! You cut your forehead!
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
(西班牙口音): 孩子们…
(with Spanish accent): Hey, kids...
如果你们有外伤
if you have an open wound,
抓一把土或者猫砂
get some dirt or kitty litter
放在伤口上揉搓就能止血啦
and rub it in there to stop the bleeding.
睡个好觉 身体就能自愈啦
Then get some sleep and wait for the body to heal itself.
现在我们都知道了
Now we know.
就像我常说的 "记住 你的知识足够了"
And like I always say: "Remember, you know enough."
G.I. Jose!
Family Guy 10x02
Seahorse Seashell Party
海马海贝派对 题目源自Yutube视频Drinking Out of Cups中的一句话
中文字幕:zurica 校对:zurica wudixny 注释:zurica wudixny 后期:zurica 压制:wudixny @familyguy贴吧字幕组
真好
Nice.
STEWIE: Brian 你在干嘛
STEWIE: Brian, what are you doing?
唉呀妈呀 Stewie
Geez, Stewie.
把我屎都吓出来了
Scared the crap out of me.
你手里拿的什么
Whatcha got there?
唉 我可以告诉你
Okay, I'll tell you;
但你得保密
but you can't tell anyone.
行…行吗 你可得保持淡定
All-All right? You have to be really cool about this.
好的 当然了
Yeah, of course.
这是一些蘑菇
These are mushrooms.
作为某种致幻药
It's a psychedelic drug.
能让你看到奇怪的东西 爽上几个小时
Makes you see weird things and feel happy for a few hours.
我估摸着咱们会被困在家里一段时间
I figure we're going to be stuck inside f a while
都怪这飓风 所以最好找点乐子
with this storm, so it'll be a fun way
…来打发时间 - 明白了
…to pass the time. - Okay.
你对这个无所谓吧
Are you gonna be cool?
哦是的 我完全没意见
Oh yeah, I'm totally cool about that.
我…我…我有很多朋友用这个
I-I-I-I have a lot of friends who do it,
他们总是愿意在我周围做这些
and they're willing to do it around me all the time,
因为他们知道我完全没意见
because they know I'm so cool about it
不对他们做评价
and I don't judge them.
所以 你懂的 请便吧…
So, you know, go ahead...
那好 我开始了
Well, here we go.
没错 我朋友也是这么说的
Yup, that's what my friends say, too.
"那好 我开始了"
"Well, here we go."
哟…伙计 我好像自己也感觉到了
Oh... dude, I think I can feel it, too.
我也被你感染"嗨"了
I'm gettin' a context high.
真无聊
I'm bored.
是啊 太没劲了
Yeah, this sucks.
我们这一整天该干嘛
What are we supposed to do all day?
哎 来玩哑谜猜字游戏怎么样
Well, how about we play charades?
哦 对呀 好的好的 我先来 我先来
Ooh! Yeah. O-okay. Me first! Me first!
看好了 是一部电影 明白吗 电影 电影
Okay, it's a movie. All right? Movie. Movie.
Peter 猜字哑谜可不能讲话
Peter, there's no talking in charades.
好吧 抱歉 抱歉
O-Okay, sorry, sorry.
Okay (小声地) 电影
Okay (whispers) Movie.
- Peter - 抱歉 抱歉
- Peter! - Sorry. Sorry.
(轻声地): 好吧 一个词
(softly): Okay, one word.
Peter 你还是在讲话
Peter, you're still talking!
好吧 好吧 这样 这样 这样
Okay, okay. Right, right, right.
《古灵侦探》
Fletch.
《古灵侦探》(1985)是一部悬疑喜剧
- 是《古灵侦探》吗 - 是的
- Is it Fletch? - It is Fletch.
你们现在想干嘛
What do you wanna do now?
我有个主意
I got an idea.
不如你们都静坐在这里
How about you all sit there quietly
听我发出"老爸式"的响声
while I make "Dad" noises?
Brah-ha-hah!
Brah-ha! Brah!
Schumai.
Myah!
…拉泡屎去
... go to the john.
老天 雨下得还真大
Boy, the rain's really comin' down.
是啊 我还从来没见过这阵势
I know, I've never seen anything like it.
不过咱们像这样呆在一起也不错啊 是吧
But it's kinda nice for us all to be together like this, huh?
(瞳孔放大是嗑药的一个反应)
那么 你们现在想做什么
So, what do you guys wanna do now?
哎 我想到了 咱们来打"手"枪
Oh, hey, I know! Let's play finger-bang.
砰 砰
Bang! Bang!
我要用"手"枪毙了你 Chris
I'm gonna finger-bang you, Chris.
没准我亲"手"先毙了你 老爸
Not if I finger-bang you first, Dad!
砰 砰
Bang! Bang!
我要同时出"手"毙了你们两个
I'm gonna finger-bang the two of you at the same time.
- 砰 砰 - 嗨 我也参加 砰
Bang! Bang! Hey, me too! Bang!
呃 没人想被你毙掉 Meg
Oh, no one wants to get finger-banged by you, Meg.
为什么你不自己毙掉自己呢 Meg
Why don't you just go do that to yourself, Meg?
我觉得我要吐了
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Brian?!
我要剪掉自己的耳朵
I'm gonna cut my ear off
画家梵高就把耳朵割了下来送给了他爱的人
来阻止第二次世界大战
to prevent World War Two.
哦 老天 哦 老天
Oh, God! Oh, God!
我想知道…
I wonder...
啊哈
Aha!
你到底想干嘛 死鬼
What the hell were you trying to do, man?!
那些蘑菇把你弄得神魂颠倒
Those mushrooms are messin' you up!
女同性恋和女聋人穿着相同
Lesbians and deaf women wear the same clothes.
是啊 是啊 肯定是的 老兄
Yeah, yeah, they sure do, buddy.
好了 冷静一点 Brian
All right, just stay calm, Brian.
你会挺过来的
You'll get through this.
我是说 你看到Lady Gaga的裸体后都挺过来了
I mean, you got through seeing Lady Gaga naked.
好了 五分钟 Ga -- 逼真大
Okay, five minutes, Miss Ga-- gina big!
模仿了Jerry Lewis(美国老牌谐星)的腔调
讽刺lady Gaga穿着实在太裸露
一会儿我把你的依云矿泉水拿来
And I will be right back with your Evian.
别担心 Brian
Don't worry, Brian.
我会一整夜都呆在你身边
I'm gonna stay by your side all night.
好吗 嘘 嘘
All right? Shh. Shh.
没事了 没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
你喜欢我治愈系的声音吗
Do you like my soothing voice?
模仿了《Annoying Orange》(一部网络喜剧)的嘴型
还…还…还给我地图
Re-re-re-re-return the map.
还…还…还给我那些你从我那里偷来的东西
Re-re-re-re-return what you have stolen from me.
恶搞了电影《Time Bandits》(时间劫匪)里的情节
不…
No...!
哎 我有个主意
Oh, hey, I got an idea.
咱们来跟着音乐唱歌吧
Let's have a sing-a-long.
好吧 我来唱一首电影里开场的追逐音乐
Okay, I'm gonna sing the opening chase music
来自《印第安纳琼斯:圣战奇兵》
from Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade.
愿意的话可以加入伴唱
Feel free to join in.
我操 Meg 你搞毛啊
Dammit, Meg! Will you stop that?!
太吵了
That is so annoying!
噢…很吵是吗
Oh... that was annoying?!
那你在这里愚蠢地 讨厌地乱哼哼就不吵吗
What about your stupid, obnoxious humming?!
Meg 别用那种语气跟你爸爸说话
Meg, don't talk to your father like that!
是啊 闭嘴 Meg
Yeah, shut up, Meg.
不 你闭嘴 Chris
No! You shut up, Chris!
我受够了你们这些人合起伙来整我
I am sick of all you guys ganging up on me!
你们都以为自己比我强多了
You guys all think you're so much better than me!
哦 Meg 这是我听过的
Oh, Meg. That is the least fancy thing
最不金贵的事情了
I have ever heard.
嘘 好了 好了 好了
Shh. There, there, there.
一切都会变好的 你没事了
Everything's gonna be fine. You're all right.
我觉得我…我快死了
I think I'm... I think I'm dying.
简 方达
Jane Fonda.
美国六七十年代的著名女星
那个…那个…那个…说对了吗
Is that... i-i-is that... is that... is that right?
是的 没错 伙计 完全是简 方达
Yeah, that's right, buddy. Totally Jane Fonda.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
你的老友Stewie在身边呢
Your pal Stewie is right here.
放松…
Just relax...
休息一下…
and get some rest...
Brian.
藏起来
Hide!
巴士的轮子 转啊转
The wheels on the bus go round and round
转啊转
Round and round
巴士的轮子 转啊转
The wheels on the bus go round and round
-   径直穿过了小镇   - Peanut(估计是想叫Peter)
-   All through the town   - Peanut!
偷窥者…
Peeper...
想做(咝咝声)爱吗…
Wanna have (hissing) sex...?
Groggety!
显然是Giggity的变音 另Quagmire的形象是石像鬼 英文是gargoyle
也许是这2个词结合而来的
LOIS (咝咝声): 舌头…舔舔我
LOIS (hissing): Slip... me some tongue.
你尝过鸡肉了吗 老兄
Did you try the chicken, buddy?
MEG蟑螂: 我想你给过我虫子了 Brian
MEG-ROACH: I think you gave me worms, Brian.
STEWIE: Brian...
Brian...
Brian!
- STEWIE: Brian. - Uh, Stewie.
呃…是Stewie吗
Eh, uh... Stewie?
是的 我在这儿
Yeah, I'm right here.
哦 老天 你的嘴唇看起来真怪
Oh, my God. Your lip looks really weird.
弄弄好行吗
Can we fix that?
把那个扒出来 呃
L-Let's get that out of there. Ew.
我太渴了
Oh, I'm so thirsty.
咱们下楼去喝点水
Let's get you downstairs so you can drink some water.
好的 走吧 伙计 给你弄点水喝
All right, let's go, buddy. Let's get you some water.
STEWIE: 好了 现在…现在 别急 别急
STEWIE: Okay, now-- Now, h-h-hold on. Hold on.
我先把碗放下来 你会弄洒的
Let me put the bowl down first. You're gonna spill it.
哇 哇 哇 慢点 慢点
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow down. Slow down.
听着 Meg 我不知道你哪根筋不对了
Look, Meg, I don't know what your problem is.
我觉得老爸哼唱的很有趣
I thought Dad's humming was pretty entertaining.
你知道吗 我正要说这个
You know what? This is what I'm talking about.
这真是个极好的例子
This is a perfect example.
你是我的哥哥
You're my brother.
你应该站在我这边
You're supposed to be on my side,
可你如此混蛋地对待我
and you're such a bastard to me.
有多混蛋
How am I a bastard?!
哟 你想听我从头说来吗
Oh, you want the full story?
- Meg 收敛点儿 - 现在不行 妈
- Meg, please. - Not now, Mom.
我觉得Brian像在那边喝水
I think Brian's getting a little water in there.
Chris 你待我好似仇人 我也不知个中缘由
Chris, you treat me like you hate me, and I don't know why.
你总是说一些伤我感情的事
You say hurtful things to me constantly.
你知道那是什么感觉吗
Do you have any idea what that feels like?
我要是对你说那些会怎样
What if I said those things to you?
我要是开始叫你肥胖的 脓包样的废柴
What if I started calling you a fat, zitty loser,
说你连个朋友都没
who has no friends
闻起来像养宠物鸟的老女人 会怎样
and smells like an old woman who has birds for pets?
还在喝
Still drinkin'.
这样的请求很过分吗
Is it too much to ask
只是要自己的兄弟体面一点对待我而已
to be treated with a little decency from my brother?
也许你能展现出对我的少许善意
Maybe show me some kind of kindness by not jumping
只要你不再跟着他们搞什么"整Meg"的把戏
on the "Let's get Meg" family bandwagon?
唉
Aw.
好了 Meg 够了
Alright, Meg, that's enough.
你演戏似的也发泄完了
You've had your little dramatic outburst.
嗨 我想到了 妈
Hey, I got an idea, Mom.
咱们来聊聊Chris的老妈 怎样
How about we talk about Chris' mother? Huh?
咱们为什么不谈谈你呢
Why don't we talk about you?
哦 得了吧
Oh, for God's sake.
听着 咱们别把这事扯大了 行吗
Look, let's not turn this into some big thing, okay?
哦…哦…
Oh... Oh...
哦 老天 感觉好多了
Oh, God, that feels so much better.
你知道 Brian 也许你是条狗
You know, Brian, you may be a dog,
可你实在是一只相当酷的猫
but you're a pretty cool cat.
Stewie说的哦
Stewie just said that!
恶搞了一个广告语
把他带回你家
Take it home with ya!
嗨…
Hey...
嗨 各位
Hey, everyone.
我感觉到了很多不和谐的气氛
I'm sensing a lot of negativity here.
怎么回事呀
What's going on?
是的 你说对了 Brian 就是这样的
Yes. You're right, Brian. There is.
看来Meg觉得她站在这里嚷嚷
Meg seems to think she's taking some kind of stand here
就能让我们感觉到亏欠她似的
that's gonna make us all feel like we're inadequate.
哎哟老天 还委屈你了吗
My God, you're condescending.
哇 看看这两个人 他们针锋相对
Geez, look at those two. They're goin' at each other
就像一个意大利男人和一个黑人妇女那样
like an Italian guy and a black woman.
嗨 你不能在这里停车
Hey, you can't park here!
你说什么
Excuse me?
画外音: 因为受到了来自天敌的正式挑战
NARRATOR: Having been officially challenged by her
这个雌性黑人准备好了战斗
natural enemy, the black female prepares for combat
她摘下了自己身上的许多环饰
by taking off her many rings.
与此同时 雄性意大利人环视四周
Meanwhile, the Italian male looks around to make sure
以确保其他雄性意大利人在周围
the other Italian males are indeed
也看到了他受到的威胁
seeing what he is seeing.
感觉到大战在即 一群犹太人
Sensing the impending battle, a flock of Jews
赶紧飞走了 因为避免争斗
flies quickly away, as avoiding confrontation
是他们最好的生存机会
is their best chance for survival.
恶搞了国家地理纪录片
听着 Meg 这里争吵的根源就是
Look, the bottom line here, Meg, is that you're just
你把自己的问题归咎于别人
taking your own problems out on everyone else.
哦 我的问题吗
Oh, my problems?
哦 我明白了
Oh, I see.
那这个问题是不是源自我的榜样老妈
Is this coming from my role model mother?
商店扒手(S04E09) 瘾君子(S04E23)
The shoplifter, the drug addict,
AV女星(S09E09) 那个让Gene Simmons(S03E20)
the porn star, the whore who let Gene Simmons
Gene Simmons是以色列裔的美籍摇滚音乐人
和Bill Clinton(S05E13)专门跑到镇里来上她的婊子
and Bill Clinton go to town on her?
哎 那又怎么样
Oh, so what?
所有这些早就过去了
All those things are behind me now.
就是因为这些经历才让我现在变得更好
I'm a better person now because of those experiences.
是吗 你变得更好了吗
Are you? Are you a better person?
- 你想说什么 Meg - 我就是想说
- What's your point, Meg? - My point is that with
正因为过去你所有的不负责任的 不计后果的
all the irresponsible, reckless,
傻逼行为 才某种程度上
idiotic behavior in your past, that somehow,
导致你现在一直用这种神经质的 傲慢的
somehow you have the nerve, the arrogance to consistently
冷漠的态度来指出我的缺点
and ruthlessly point out my shortcomings.
好吧 好吧 说够了没
Alright, well, fine, okay?
我要不是好母亲 那谁是
I'm not the perfect mother. Who is?
呵呵 你不仅不是好母亲
Oh, not only are you not the perfect mother.
你跟好母亲的标准可差远了
You're the farthest thing from.
自从你生出我那刻起 我就只能信赖你
From the moment you gave birth to me, I had to trust you.
我别无选择
I had no choice.
我需要你在这世上保护我
I needed you to protect me from the world.
引导我 为我指点迷津
To... to be my guide, to help me navigate the difficult,
小心呵护我的成长历程
confusing, and vulnerable journey to becoming a person.
而这些事情你一件都没做过
You have done none of those things.
你是我的母亲 你得到了一个孩子的信任
You're my mother, and you took a child's trust
可你却在做母亲的17年里把它打得粉碎
and smashed it into bits in a 17-year-long mission
还要作践一颗早已被你扼杀的心
to destroy something that you killed a long time ago.
说老实话 等我18岁了…
And honestly, when I turn 18...
我…我都不知道还想不想看到你这张脸
I-I don't know that I ever want to see you again.
哇哦 每个人都在推特上转发
Oh wow, everybody's already tweeting
"Stewie说的哦"
"Stewie Just Said That."
你说的对
You're right.
你说的对 我是个糟糕的母亲
You're right. I'm a terrible mother.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我真的 真的很抱歉 Meg
I'm so, so sorry, Meg.
你还能原谅我吗
Can you ever forgive me?
哦 老天
Oh, God.
而且你从来不让老爸搅拌油漆玩
And you never let Dad stir the paint anymore,
鬼知道你说什么
whatever that means.
我不知道你还记得呢 Meg
I didn't know you knew that, Meg,
不过我很高兴你提出来了(装清纯哦)
but I'm glad you brought it up.
哦 Meg 我不知道该说什么
Oh, Meg, I don't know what to say.
你对我的指责都是对的
All of those things you said about me are true.
我对你一直是个不称职的妈妈
I have been a very bad mother to you.
我没话说
I have no excuse.
我就总是有可怕的 不可抑制的冲动
I just have this horrible, overwhelming desire
想要指出你的错误
to point out faults in you.
我不知道这冲动是哪里来的
I don't know where it comes from.
也许因为我骨子里
Maybe it's because I'm self-conscious
就想成为一个坏妈妈
about being a bad parent.
我真是 打心底反感自己的行为
I'm just, I'm so disgusted with my behavior.
我真的很抱歉 Meg
And I'm so sorry, Meg.
是啊 你就是贱
Yeah, you're a bitch.
呃 是这样 我 我还有点犹豫
Well, you know, I, I been sorta just hangin' back here,
要不要掺合进来 因为我觉得自己
takin' all this in, 'cause I didn't think
没带上一条狗就参战有点冒失(⊙﹏⊙b汗)
I had a dog in this fight,
不过我的钱放在那本《哈利波特》上面
but my money's on Harry Potter over there.
哟 你觉得这很有趣吗 死胖子
Oh, you think that's funny, fat ass?
呃 我不知道这算不算有趣
Well, I don't know if it's funny.
我…我只是觉得蛮明智的
I-I think it's clever.
我是说 你…你戴着副大眼镜站在那儿…
I mean, y-y-you got the big glasses there...
我…我不知道 跟我说说 说说你怎么想
I-I-I don't know. T-T-Tell me, tell me what's on your mind.
好吧 跟你说说 自私鬼老爸先生
Oh, I'll tell you, Mister Selfish-ass Dad.
哎 那我就回敬你"自私鬼老爸先生"先生
Hey. That's "Mister Mister selfish-ass Dad"
小姑娘
to you, young lady.
唉呀 接下来她要针对我了吧
Oh God, is she gonna do me next?
你完全就是个自私的
You are completely selfish,
完全不负责任的父亲
and totally irresponsible as a father.
好吧 我弄明白这是怎么回事了
All right, I see what's goin' on here.
你是爱上你的老豆了(⊙﹏⊙b汗)
You're in love with your old man.
你没受过教育 也没钱
You have no education, you have no interests,
你想做什么就不计后果地去做
you just do whatever reckless thing you want to do
从来都不考虑别人
whenever you want to do it without regard for anyone else.
哦 哦 要是你不在外面祸害街坊邻居
Oh, oh, and when you're not terrorizing the community
整一些冒冒失失的恶作剧
with your impulsive escapades,
你就在家里成了一个彻头彻尾的混蛋
you're being a total jerk to your family.
你把女儿的脸塞进自己屁股然后放屁
You shove your daughter's face in your ass and you fart on it.
要是在外面别人
If someone in the outside world
看见你这样对我 你肯定坐牢了
could see the way you treat me, you would be in jail!
哦 呵呵 对你来说很好笑
Oh, ha ha. Oh, this is amusing to you.
好吧 看我这么说你还觉得好笑不
Well, see if you find this funny.
这事变得更有意思了
I like where this is going.
你就是个肥胖的 懒惰的 没节制的
You are a fat, lazy, abusive,
蓝领爱尔兰裔天主教老爹
blue-collar Irish Catholic dad
一沾酒就不要命
who drinks way too much
却几乎挣不了足够的钱来养家
and barely makes enough money to support his family.
你活了大半辈子
You've lived half your life,
有什么能拿得出手
and you have nothing to show for it.
你唯一有点争议的成就是你的几个孩子
Your only arguable accomplishments are your kids,
- 正眼看看我们 我们都是杯具啊 - 呃 说话小心点
- and look at us; we're a disaster. - Eh, watch it.
你从各方面来说 都是一个
You're a total and complete embarrassment
不折不扣的窘货
in every possible way.
撒泡尿照照自己 Peter Griffin
Take a good look at yourself, Peter Griffin.
你就是个人渣
You're a waste of a man.
慢着 这是在批评我
Wait a second, these are criticisms.
嗨 Lois 叫她收敛点儿
Hey, Lois, tell her to knock it off.
哎 刚才她指责我的时候 你在干什么
Oh, and where the hell were you when she was laying into me?
我在想象着得到一根精致的手杖
I was thinking about getting a fancy cane.
也可能被陌生人吸引了注意力
Maybe getting more attention from strangers.
你们俩到底有没有认真听我讲话
Have either of you guys been listening to me?
你们的脑袋是长在屁股上的吗
Do you both just have your heads up your asses?
老爸是的 你看 他耳朵上还有屎呢
Dad did! Look, he's got crap on his ears!
跟那没关系
That's unrelated.
Chris 我可不喜欢你这么说
Chris, I don't like that language.
哎哟 我也不喜欢你做的饭
Well, I don't like your cooking.
好吧 那我更不喜欢在洗衣服的时候
Well, I don't like having to literally empty
还得一点点掏干净你口袋里的狗屁玩意儿
the farts out of your pockets whenever I do your laundry.
你做饭也只会烧一种菜
You're the one who's always cookin'
小圆白菜炒花椰菜
Brussels sprouts and broccoli.
这两种菜混在一起就像爱尔兰酒吧里的斗殴
It's like an Irish bar fight down there.
你是从镇子那头来的 所以我讨厌你的品性
You're from one town over, so I hate your guts.
为什么我们从来都吃不到一点好菜
Why don't we ever get any good food?!
对啊 Bonnie都给Joe做神奇面包呢
Yeah, Bonnie gives Joe Wonder Bread.
神奇面包是美国常见的白面包品牌
好吧 那你去Bonnie家住吧
Well, then go live at Bonnie's house.
这样我还能睡踏实一点
Then I could finally sleep in
不用在早晨五点钟回答你那愚蠢的问题
and not have to answer your stupid questions at 5:00 a.m.
人家早晨好奇心重嘛
My curiosity peaks in the morning!
你把我的Dannon酸奶都喝光了
You eat all my Dannon yogurts!
我又没看见你在上面写名字了
I don't see your name on 'em!
你压根就不喜欢那酸奶 可你知道我喜欢
You don't even like them! But you know I do,
你就是不想让我喝
and you don't want me to have them!
你知道 我从来没有在这件事上责问过你
You know, I've never confronted you on it,
可我通常也是这么想的 Peter
but I've often thought the same thing, Peter.
没错 他就是那么做的
Yeah, that's exactly what he does!
因为他就是个自私的 肥胖的傻逼
'Cause he's a selfish, fat idiot!
你们都闭嘴
You shut up, all of yous!
我又没想生在这个家里(⊙﹏⊙b汗)
I didn't ask to be in this family!
唉 我来搞定他
Ugh, I'll go get him.
Peter 你给我回来
Peter? You come back here!
我的高潮都是装的(男的还能假装么...)
I faked all my orgasms!
嗨
Hey.
怎么样了
What's goin' on?
我说 那可真是 呃 屌爆了
You know, that was, uh, that was pretty cool
你终于在每个人面前挺直腰板了
the way you finally stood up to everybody.
我不知道 Brian
I don't know, Brian.
我是指 我是指我刚说的每一句话都发自内心 可…
I mean, I, I meant every word of it, but...
- 你也看到发生什么了 - 什么意思
- you saw what happened. - What do you mean?
他们互相指责 就像一群饿狼
They all turned on each other like a pack of wolves.
呃 那又怎样 不是你的错
Well, so what? That's not your problem.
你觉得有没有可能…
Do you think it's possible that...
这个家庭少了某个…
that this family can't survive without some sort of
出气筒来纾解所有的不快 就没法维持下去了
lightning rod to absorb all the dysfunction?
呃 这可真是…
Well, that's a...
有点道理 可能吧
that's a theory, I guess.
我是说 虽然不合我的愿景 但那也是重要的一部分
I mean, it-- it's not ideal, but it's an important piece
也许是我命中注定的
that maybe it's just my lot in life to provide.
也许我感觉不好了 他们感觉就好了
Maybe if I feel bad, they don't have to.
哇
Wow.
你可真是 令人难以置信的高尚和成熟 Meg
You know, that's incredibly noble and mature, Meg.
我想你可能是
You know, I think you might be
这家里最坚强的人了
the strongest person in this house.
你说真的吗 Brian
You mean that, Brian?
绝对说真的
Absolutely.
妈 爸
Mom? Dad?
- 老爸 - 走开
- Dad? - Go away!
老爸 出来吧
Dad, come out of there.
不 我不配 我就该和这些鞋子生活在一起
No! I don't deserve no better than livin' with the shoes!
Peter 原来你在这儿
Peter, there you are.
各位 我有话要讲
You guys, I have something to say.
你们是对的 都是我的错
You're right. It's all my fault.
- 什么 - 老妈 你就是最棒的妈妈
- What? - Mom, you're an amazing mother
所有我对你的指责都是一时糊涂的气话
and all the things I said about you were out of anger,
我并不是真的要表达那些意思
and I didn't mean any of them.
Chris 你是个能干的哥哥
Chris, you're an outstanding brother.
我那样说你 只会让我更加成为一个糟糕的妹妹
What I said about you was more about me being a rotten sister.
还有老爸 我非常抱歉让你如此难过
And Dad, I'm so sorry that I made you feel this way.
我不该这样对待你
You don't deserve it.
你们都没有错
None of you have done anything wrong.
我把自己所有的问题都按在了你们身上
I took all my problems out on you guys,
那不公平
and that wasn't fair.
哦 这么说都怪你了 跟我们没关系
Oh, so this was all about you, it wasn't about us.
是的
Yeah.
好吧 这才像话嘛
Alright, that makes sense.
看 我就觉得自己是坏老爹的说法很扯淡
See, I thought it was weird that I was a bad dad.
Meg 你怎么能这么耍大家
Meg, how could you put us all through that?
我很抱歉 大伙儿
I'm sorry, you guys.
你就是个臭婊子
You're a (bleep) bitch!
是的
Yes.
我就是个臭婊子(爱死Meg了)
Yes, I am.
嗨 我是Stewie Griffin 今晚的《恶搞之家》
Hi, I'm Stewie Griffin. Tonight's Family Guy
是有关毒品使用的非常特别的一集
was a very special episode about drug use.
不过最明显的事实是 这集没有笑料
But the simple fact is, it's no laughing matter.
要了解更多毒品的信息 访问你们本地的图书馆
To learn more about drugs, visit your local library.
那儿可能就有个家伙背地里出售毒品
There's probably a guy behind there who sells drugs.
晚安
Good night.
中文字幕: zurica 校对: zurica wudixny 注释: zurica wudixny 后期:zurica 压制: wudixny @familyguy贴吧字幕组